Hey guys! Let's play catch!
Yoy!
It's no fun without Match!
What a horrible place. The Tiny Loser Chamber
must be for Match!
Yeah, Ice Cube. You're a good person,
but Match is WAY BETTER!
Wha?
Match is way better, by a mile!
Pencil:
Icy, compared to Match... you're garbage.
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Ice Cube, Leafy, Eraser and Firey.
Last episode you four had the lowest scores.
The voters have voted.
Let's see which of the four of you will be eliminated.
I really hope Ice Cube doesn't get eliminated!
She doesn't deserve to.
Yeah, yeah, blah blah, whatever.
Hey, that was mean!
Are you ready yet?
Y-yeah?
Okay, then.
First, I'd like to point out, that
we have a large crowd watching this event today.
So, we got 220 votes. David?
Yeah?
For some reason, 39 people voted exclusively for you.
Aw, seriously?
Voters, David was someone you
were not allowed to vote for.
Anyway, I have ten nickels.
No cake this time!?
Nope.
Moving on. If you get a nickel, you are safe for this episode.
If you don't, you will be eliminated.
That's harsh!
So the seven of you who did not fall
into the bottom four are safe from elimination.
There are only three nickels remaining.
Leafy, you only got 20 votes, so you are safe.
Yeah!
Firey, with a measly 29 votes, you are also safe.
Yay!
There is only one nickel left.
Ice Cube, Eraser, one of you will be eliminated.
[DRUMROLL]
[CYMBAL CRASH]
Eraser, goodbye.
Ice Cube, you get to stay for another day...
...or not.
So, now with Eraser gone, you are the final ten again.
Everyone:
Yaaay!
As a reward, you get another half of a pair of scissors.
Ooh, so now I have two!
Nice scissors, huh?
Firey:
Yeah!
[ERASER SIGHS]
This screen is currently showing your scores.
But at the end of this episode, the three people
with the lowest scores will be up for elimination.
Moving on, try to guess what's under this blanket.
- Bonus points!
- A mini version of Dream Island!
- A previously eliminated contestant!
- A dead body!
Hmm... a barf bag, and... a taco.
Hold on, Firey, you're right.
Ooooh!
In this episode, you each have a choice
on what contest you would like to participate in.
You can choose between Barf Bag-
-or Taco.
I will choose the taco contest.
Bubble, Ice Cube, and Pencil:
We choose the barf bag!
Hmm... that's a tough choice. I will say taco.
I also think that tacos are quite delicious.
Bleh!
Taco!
Barf bag! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
I choose the one with the taco.
So now you all have chosen.
Let's start with the barf bag contest.
You're all floating in a large barf bag.
For every second you stay on top of your island, you earn one point.
Go.
OMG! Bubble, is that actually vomit?
No, it's colored water.
Bleh!
Nevermind!
Eeeeew! This is so gross!
OMG, Rocky, why did you have to do that!?
Grrrr!
Huah!
That was mean, Pencil!
Huh! Huuyah!
- Ice Cube: Ahhh!
- Bubble: Oi!
- Pencil: Huah!
OMG, a leak!
Hueh...
Pencil:
Yay!
Whatever.
Grrr!
Ehhhya!
Bubble! Let's make ice cream!
Cone, ice, flavoring, whipped cream!
And voila! Taste it!
Eleeehhh!
[BUBBLE GRUMBLES AND CHOKES]
Yuck! This tastes absolutely terrible! This is garbage!
Oh no!
Ahhhhhhh!
Well, that happened quickly.
Now it's time for the Taco contest.
Which is? See, I'm filling in for Eraser.
Try to make a taco.
Announcer:
You can use any ingredients you want.
Go.
Okay, so I'll need a tortilla, some lettuce, a tomato...
I'm really glad I didn't choose the Taco contest.
Huh? Why not?
You know what? I-I don't wanna hear
any stupid questions right now.
Hey Leafy, why are you making such a big taco?
So if anyone is having trouble making a
taco themselves, I can lend some!
Oh, so, is it like you do it for me?
Uhh, I guess so?
Yeah, I got myself a servant right here!
Grrr!
So, how much do I gotta pay?
TWO HUNDRED VIGINTILLION DOLLARS!
Well, what do you know?
Mbueh, mbueh, RUEH, RRUH, RUH!
Huehhh...
Aw, now I have to start all over again!
I'm done.
That's good.
Me too!
Wow! Armless people are ahead.
Here, take it.
Here's my taco.
Mine too!
Come on, Firey. Hurry up!
Okay, I'm done.
Here's my taco. I-it's a bit burnt, though.
So all five of you have finished.
Tennis Ball, you finished first.
Let's see how good your taco is.
The ten eliminated contestants will taste your taco.
You'll get 10 points for each person who likes your taco.
The results are coming in.
Let's see what they have to say.
Tennis Ball, exactly half of the
eliminated contestants like your taco.
I was expecting a bit more,
considering the fact that you've been
feeding them only bread for the past 13 months.
Whatever.
Spongy is next.
Woo! Good job, Spongy!
Even though you'd used your feet to make your taco,
8 people liked it.
Yaaay!
Leafy, you had the largest taco.
That's pretty good. I'll take it.
Up next is Pen.
To guarantee you're staying here for
one more episode, you need at least 4 likes.
Come on, come on!
What?!
People can tell when you've cheated.
Awww...
Firey, hello.
Hello.
You are the last person, you know.
Yeah.
Bubble and Rocky are already
guaranteed to be in the danger zone.
Either you or Pen will join them.
Firey, to beat Pen and get out of the
danger zone, you need at least 6 likes.
6 likes, okay.
Let's see how you did.
Yes!
No!
I guess eliminated contestants like burnt food,
you know all crispy and everything.
So that means that Pen, Bubble and Rocky
fall into the danger zone.
So the voting will only be between the three of them.
People, vote off which one you think
should be eliminated from the Battle for Dream Island.
So, I guess they aren't sending us any more tacos?